DANIEL STANGAR

CONTACT

dstangar@gmail.com

Daniel Stangar 7 Dorset Gardens East Grinstead RH19 2SD West Sussex

07547 277 299

WEB DEVELOPING SKILLS:

- Python
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Basics of VueJS
- Firestore database

PROFILE

I am a 57 years old man from Prague, Czechoslovakia. I have been living in the UK since 2012 and I have acquired British citizenship in 2019. I am married with one child. Since May 2020 I have been studying and practicing web development at home. Over the period of my home study I found that the more I learn, the more web development related problems I am able to solve.

The coding works I did so far can be seen on Github:

https://github.com/DanielStangar?tab=repositories

Or you can look directly at the websites I have been working on so far and keep developing:

https://g-universal.com/Alpha18/

https://g-universal.com/EMPTY%20DESK/

https://g-universal.com/DODO/

https://g-universal.com/ToDo%201/

https://g-universal.com/Flowers%20Club/

https://g-universal.com/Cavendish%20Cars/index.html

EXPERIENCE

Self-employed owner of a taxi business Alpha 18 Cars, East Grinstead and Chailey, Mid-Sussex — 2013-Present

My business partner retired in 2018 and I inherited the taxi business from him. Here I have learned about enterprising and customer services.

Counsellor and Lecturer - 2003-2012

During those years I was working on humanitarian projects under I HELP International in India and South Africa. I was helping people in difficult life situations.

Translator and Interpreter — 1996-2002

After apprenticeship in New Era Publication, Copenhagen, I was translating from Czech to English and English to Czech, mostly in Prague. I have translated four books, many contract agreements and materials for self-improvement courses. As a translator and interpreter I have learnt to study efficiently, be detail oriented and public speaking.

System Administrator — 1994-1996

I worked in SWIFT department as a system administrator and worked with the computer system for international payments.

Light and Sound Technician — 1985-1993

I worked first two years in TV and then in various theatres run by Prague Municipal Council.

EDUCATION

CODING CERTIFICATES

My certificates for HTML, CSS, JS and Python can be seen on stuioweb.com website.

When you click the link below, you will see my profile. On the top are the courses I have studied and below them are the certificates I attained in this school.

https://school.studioweb.com/profile/dstangar_1089

FURTHER CODING CERTIFICATES:

Vue JS3: Composition API (with Pinia, Firebase9 & Vite)

Getting started with Firebase 9

Pinia Crash Course

Vue 3 Animations

My education in Czechoslovakia:

Secondary Technical School of Communication Current — equivalent of A levels, graduated in 1985

GCSE equivalent, completed in 1981

My education in UK:

GA Level 5 Certificate in Teaching English as a Foreign Language in 2019 B1 English Language Certificate

EF SET Certificate English Level Listening - C1, Reading - C2